live-tennis.eu 2019-06-17

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context.

### What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website ?

We do not collect personal information from visitors of our site. We only provide articles and information.  
However, when visitors wish to contact us using the contact form, the e-mail of the visitor is stored in the mailbox of our webmaster.

### When do we collect information ?

We collect the visitor e-mail when visitors use the contact form.

### How do we use your information ?

When visitors use the contact form, the visitor e-mail address is solely used by the webmaster to reply. The visitor e-mail address will never be transmitted to any third party.

### Right to be forgotten

If at any time you would like us to delete the e-mails exchanged using the contact form, you can drop us a message with your e-mail and we will promptly remove **ALL** correspondence.

### How do we protect visitor information?

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

### Do we use 'cookies'?

Yes. See our [Cookie Policy](https://live-tennis.eu/cookie-policy).

### Third Party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Advertising

We use Google AdSense, Criteo and Ezoic Advertising on our website. As a third party vendors, they use cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

### Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?

It's important to note that we allow third party behavioral tracking for advertising purpose and internal analytics reporting.

#####   
Last Edited on June 5, 2018
